Downloaded @ subs4free.club
- Where do you want this, Ma?
- Here on the counter.
Vinny, what happened to your face?
It's nothin', you should see the other guy.
Why you do the fighting?
Why you no play the golf that you like?
That's a rich guy's sport, Ma.
Once I turn pro, I'll be able
to play golf all the time.
And buy you and Pop anything you want.
Vinny, I already got everything I want.
I know, I know.
- Make sure you got enough for us next week.
- Sure, sure, no problem, gentlemen.
I sell you all the sugar,
all the yeast you need.
More guys from the Genna mob?
Don't worry about them. They just
need ingredients to make the booze.
So maybe you shouldn't be sellin'
your homemade wine right now.
You don't want them thinkin'
that you're their competition.
Competition? It's no competition.
Nobody make better wine than I do.
- Plus, hey, we need the money.
- Yeah, I know, Pop.
Hey, this crazy prohibition
these politicians make...
...it's an opportunity for everybody.
And why we come to America?
Opportunity.
I know, I know, I know.
All right, I gotta go for a run, okay?
I gotta be in tip-top shape for tomorrow.
Come on, O'Malley!
My grandma hits harder than that.
He's done.
Jesus, I thought we were supposed
to be sparring in here.
Sorry, Sergeant, I got carried away.
Yeah, take it easy, Jack!
O'Malley's jaw swells up...
...he won't be able to eat
any donuts for a week.
Yeah, fuck you, Landa.
He's got a good left hand.
Lookin' good, Jack. Lookin' real good.
Thank you.
- You ready for tomorrow night?
- Are you kiddin', that's my big debut.
Just wish it was a sanctioned event.
Can't have 'em in Chicago
anymore like they do back east.
Nah, that's okay.
A charity event for veterans,
what could be better?
You're gonna be there, right?
- Wouldn't miss it.
- Swell.
Look, I gotta get in the shower.
I gotta go to the store and see my pop.
- Sorry again, Sergeant.
- Yeah, yeah.
He's hits like a mule
considering how young he is.
Is that your excuse, Bob?
- Even your hookers don't go down that fast.
- Yeah, fuck you.
And in the other corner,
fighting for the Irish...
...making his big debut,
Battling Jack McGurn!
- Here's our boy.
- Jackie!
Come on, Jack!
Well, well, look who's here. Capone.
- A little far from the south side, isn't he?
- Fight fans go where the fights are, huh?
Hey, you don't think
he's here to gamble, do you?
A fine upstanding citizen like him?
No, he's taking another poor
orphan boy to his first sporting event.
I feel bad I misjudged him.
Frankie!
Grazie, mama.
The bread's a little tough.
Papa told me you knocked the guy's block off.
Yep. It even bounced around
the canvas a few times.
- Vinny!
- What, I'm only kidding!
It's a figure of speech.
Hey, why don't you tell your mama
what happened next?
What?
Well, there were some promoters
at the fight tonight.
They said after a few more tune-ups,
they're gonna put me on the pro fight card...
...out in Aurora.
That's my boy!
Here's to the next welterweight
champion of the world!
- Salud!
- Salud.
No, no.
You think we're stupid?
We know what you're doin'.
- What?
- Nobody sells liquor on the West Side...
...except the Genna family!
This is the only warning you're gonna get.
What time you got?
It's a little before ten.
You want me to take over?
Nah, I don't mind driving.
You get used to these Canadian
runs after a while.
I gotta say, Torrio's fuckin' right,
it's worth the drive.
Especially compared to that
bathtub shit people drink.
What's this?
You havin' trouble?
No...
...you are.
Buddy, just take a minute.
You don't know whose truck this is.
Sure I do, it's mine.
Look, this is the south side.
This is Johnny Torrio's territory.
You gotta be crazy!
Well, I've heard that before.
Sometimes people even call me 'Bugs'.
Fuck. It's Bugs Moran.
- You're with the O'Banion mob.
- That's right.
Only Mr. O'Banion
doesn't just run the north side.
Now he runs the south side,
west side, all sides.
Make sure your tell Torrio that. Get out.
Tell him we said thanks.
We appreciate you doin' all the drivin'.
And thanks for the new truck.
Tough break, kid.
I don't suppose the purse was too big either.
The big money goes to the guys
at the top of the card.
- Name's Al, by the way.
- Jack.
No, you're not.
Been asking around about you.
Your name's Vinny Demory.
What's with the name change?
If you've been around the fight game...
...you know for some reason
people don't go for Italian boxers.
But the Irish?
They love 'em.
So I told the police at the gym
that my name was Jack McGurn...
...and they said, "welcome, kid, come on in."
Smart. Stupid micks.
So, how'd you like to make
some real money, Jack?
How do you mean?
- My boss, Mr. Torrio.
- Johnny Torrio?
Mr. Torrio is always lookin' for smart guys
who know how to climb up the ladder.
Yeah, well, my pop's got enough
trouble with the Gennas as it is.
The Gennas? They're bums.
They'll get theirs some day.
I just don't want to get involved
with guns or nothin'.
Who said anything about guns?
With those mitts of yours?
We're just lookin' for a little bit
of protection for our drivers.
You want to help out your family, don't you?
Yeah, of course.
So what do you say?
Look, if you don't like it, no hard feelings.
I tell ya, this prohibition, it's the best
thing that ever happened to me.
Yeah?
That's funny, my pop says the same thing.
What the hell?
Step out of the truck please.
- What's in the truck?
- Groceries.
Oh, yeah? The liquid kind? Let's take a look.
Come on, guys. Is that really necessary?
Shut your mouth, alright? We're going
to have to confiscate this truck.
So, what's the tally?
Just under a hundred
thousand dollars this month.
- That's it?
- No, that can't be right.
What about all the booze
we've been swipin' from Capone?
We're saving a bundle not having
to buy own own trucks!
It's really none of my business,
Mr. O'Banion...
...but Torrio and Capone are still
bringing in more money than you are...
...and it's largely due to their brothels.
If you're asking me.
Well, I didn't!
But if you ask me, I'll tell you this.
Booze is one thing...
...but the holy mother would never
forgive me for startin' cathouses up here.
That may be okay for those spaghetti
bendin' pimps, but not for me!
As a matter of fact, I'll bet that
some of the boys on our payroll...
...chasin' wops out of
this neighborhood right now!
These books are being cooked,
you will be, too.
Cheers.
See, what did I yell ya?
I knew I had it handled.
So, nice work, young man.
Thank you, Mr. Torrio.
Want a taste of Canada's finest?
No, thanks.
I'm still in training for my fights.
An Italian that doesn't drink.
Okay.
So what do you like?
You like gambling, like women, what?
I never had no money for gambling...
...or women, for that matter.
We got a ton of whorehouses
on the south side, my treat.
Yeah, but you have to watch out because
you're not gonna find one whore...
...in any of those places that this mamaluc'
hasn't already fucked and tainted.
Hey, you gotta test 'em out,
make sure they know what they're doin'.
Nah, that's okay.
What do you like?
You like nightclubs? You like music?
- You mean like jazz?
- Sure.
- Yeah, I love jazz.
- Alright, alright. Al...
...you have take this young man
to The Four Deuces, it's all my treat.
Okay, Torrio.
Where?
This, this is Torrio's place, enjoy yourself.
Besides, I gotta see some professional
ladies who could use my company.
Have fun, kid.
- For you, sir?
- Club soda.
- Hey, doll, let me buy you a drink.
- Get your paws off.
- It's just a drink.
- I said leave me alone!
I think the lady said
that she's not interested.
Fuck you.
Come on.
My hero.
Nah, you probably could've
handled him yourself.
- Lulu.
- Jack.
Okay, it's Louise,
but I'm trying to be a model.
I think Lulu sounds sexier,
what do you think?
Can I buy you a drink, Lulu?
No thanks, I brought my own.
Well.
You dance?
Thank you, thank you.
Well, thanks for the dance, handsome.
- I gotta go.
- Oh, wait, wait.
When can I see you again?
Honey...
...based on this ten dollar suit,
I don't think you can afford me.
But good luck with the boxing, slugger.
- Sun's gonna be up in a bit, huh?
- Yeah.
- I ain't never pulled an all-nighter before.
- Really? Welcome to the club.
You know, if you come work for us full time,
you can come to the club whenever you want.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I don't know, I just can't.
Really? Okay, okay.
Look, if you ever change your mind,
there's a whole lotta money to be made...
...especially for that family of yours.
Thanks, Al.
Let's go, Al.
You thought you could
muscle in on our territory?
Angelo?
Angelo! Angelo!
Ma? Ma!
Vinny!
What... what happened?
Sorry, kid, somebody popped your old man.
What?
Your mother said she never seen them before.
She probably can't identify them.
Listen, I'm going to be honest with you guys.
There's probably nothing we can do here.
What are you talking about?
It was the Genna family, I know it was.
Hey, hey, hey, look, kid.
The Gennas know very important people
on this side of town and you know that.
Yeah, just like all the cops
they bought off to look the other way.
Shut your mouth!
Looky, looky, looky what the cat dragged in.
Aren't you boys a little far
from your precinct?
I mean, we're not here
to help you find the killers.
Because we know you're gonna
have a drink with them tonight.
Don't you two got something better to do?
Like, maybe pick up some more bag money?
Is that what you call it?
We heard about it on the police radio.
They steal anything, money?
You recognize 'em?
The car, anything?
No.
Alright.
It's those two clowns precinct, so on
this, our hands are kind of tied but...
I understand.
You don't hesitate
to give us a call, alright, kid?
Ma'am.
The police, they're going to find
the men who do this, yes?
No, they're not gonna do nothin'.
Hey, boss, someone to see you.
Hey, Jack, sit down.
Does that offer still stand?
Yes, I gotta warn you,
things are starting to heat up.
Mike Merlo had done a good job
at the head of the Sicilian Union...
...keepin' peace between the families.
The problem is...
...Mike died a couple days ago from cancer.
Right afterwards, the micks
started shootin' up our drivers.
I'll do whatever you want on one condition.
You give me the names
of the men who killed my father.
Welcome, Jack.
We can't very well
keep going the way we have.
The killings, the violence,
it's not good for business.
Violence is my business.
And I fought for every inch
I own in this city.
I'm no stranger to violence either, Dion.
I wanted to meet with you, Johnny...
...because I agree.
All these killings are getting out of hand.
Why don't we staunch the flow
of blood running through our streets.
There's plenty of customers for both of us.
I'll tell you what.
This here brewery is more than I need.
We've got plenty of others.
Why don't you take it off my hands.
Good.
Well.
- So, no more violence?
- Salud.
- Cheers.
You're not training anymore?
I got a new job.
And a new suit.
So how's the modeling business?
I went out to California for a few weeks.
- It didn't work out.
- No?
No.
They don't know what they're doin'
if they let you get away.
Oh, yeah?
The first thing I want to do is get
rid of all O'Banion's piss water.
I'm gonna bring in the best hops,
the best malt...
...all the ingredients we need to make
the best goddamn beer in Chicago.
Then once we get up and running here...
...we should be making over
a million dollars a year, easy.
Alright, boys, let's take her down.
Get over there!
- What the hell is this?
- Alright, nobody move, FBI, this is a bust!
- Who the hell are you, you got a warrant?
- Yes.
I tell you, you're wasting your time!
This is just a waste of your time.
O'Banion set me up, alright?
Whatever he's paying you, I'll double it.
See?
I'm a man of my word, no more violence.
Why waste bullets on ignorant greaseballs
when you can just have them arrested?
Like taking candy from a baby.
Or liquor from a wop.
And, you know, now with Torrio gone...
...I'm going to make sure the next head
of the Sicilian Union is one of our own.
You know, there's another good
thing about Mike Merlo dying.
Yeah, what's that?
Well, what does everyone do
when there's a funeral?
They buy flowers.
Don't worry, I wouldn't turn you in.
I been in enough trouble
with the law as it is.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I accidentally killed a guy once.
I got loaded...
...took out my old man's car,
went for a joy ride.
I hit another guy's car.
Why aren't you in jail?
My daddy's got money,
knew the right judge to give it to.
Jeez.
I guess I'll be doin'
the driving from now on.
Oh, yeah?
Are you taking me places?
Anywhere you want to go.
Fuckin' rat! That Irish fuckin' rat!
What, fuckin' sells Torrio his brewery
and then runs and tells the feds?
And then tries to put Angelo Genna
at the head of the Sicilian family?
He's a fuckin' dead man!
Do you fuckin' hear me!
- Don't you think we should wait till Torrio...
- What are you interrupting me for?
There's a lot of people buying flowers
for Mike Merlo's funeral.
You two know what to do.
Jack, you're drivin'.
Go!
Keep the motor runnin'.
Hello, Dion.
You're here for Mike's funeral, I take it.
There you are.
Among other things, you dirty mick.
No!
Alright, come on, Jackie,
let's move, let's move.
Go, go, go!
Johnny Torrio, I am sentencing you...
...to nine months in the Lake County jail.
Request that my client have 48 hours
to put his affairs in order?
Granted.
So you're saying you
have no idea who did this?
Boys, we're trying to help you out here.
We're trying to give you a break...
...we know this wasn't a robbery.
You know how this city got its name?
The Indians.
When they came here...
...there was nothin', except for swamp...
...cabbage weeds.
They called it 'Chi-ca-gou'...
...which means 'bad smell'.
See, no matter how hard
you boys try to clean it up...
...this place...
...will always be rotten.
Well, we're gonna keep tryin'.
So... if you can think of anything,
you just give us a call, here's our card.
Alright, there you go.
Those motherfuckers.
Those greasy wop motherfuckers!
Right here in his own shop!
They kill a man while he's selling flowers...
...for Mike Merlo's funeral.
One of their kind!
They want a war?
- Well, they just got one!
- If you elect me as your mayor...
...I vow that I will put an end...
...to these criminal gangs that have
been taking over our fair city.
- Great, this is exactly what we need.
- I will shut down...
...these speakeasys
and gambling parlors and brothels.
- This guy's a schmuck.
- And I will put an end...
- I hate this neighborhood, John.
- I know.
- You promised we would move.
- We will, we will.
I want a bigger house when we do.
Look, it's only nine months, alright?
I'll be back before you know it.
- I want to go back to the old country.
- We'll talk about that later.
So long, Johnny.
Boss!
Boss, we gotta go!
Papers, papers! Get all your papers!
Papers! Get your papers!
I don't how, but he survived.
He's resting in his bed.
- I wanna talk to him.
- All right.
Johnny.
I...
I guess I'm not as quick
on my feet as I used to be, huh?
I got careless.
No, no, you didn't.
Don't worry about it,
doctor says you're gonna be fine.
In a couple of weeks when you get out...
...I'm gonna go track those Irish fucks down.
No.
Al, come here.
Come here.
What did he whisper to you?
He just made me the boss
of the whole south side.
So...
...it looks like I'm gonna
need a first lieutenant.
How about it, Jackie?
Anything you need, Al.
Chicago's gangland
violence continues to soar...
Since the first of this year
there's been 27 gangland killings...
...and not one conviction.
Any witness to come forward
would be number 28, that's why.
Now this bloody rivalry has gotten
to the point where someone's going to talk.
Sooner or later, someone will talk.
You wanna stop the killings,
you gotta end prohibition.
That's up to congress, isn't it?
But in the meantime...
...we'll enforce the laws
that are on the books.
Okay, boys, get to it.
I bet you mugs were wondering
why I brought you down here.
Who wants to take it for a roll?
The Pony Inn.
Bugs Moran's good pals, the O'Donnels.
Get 'em up, everybody hands up! Hands up!
Get your hands up!
Don't even move a fuckin' muscle!
Come on! Jack, come on!
It's Capone's work.
Christ, my boys were entertaining
the state's attorney tonight...
...he's dead.
The feds'll be on us, now.
I don't imagine Capone's gang's gonna stop.
And they'll be comin' for your clubs next.
Oh, hell no.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
If Capone wants to play with the big toys...
...we'll just have to join in on the fun.
You better come grab some
of this before I finish it all.
Daddy?
I said come and join me.
What's wrong?
Nothin'.
You haven't been yourself since last night.
Before I used to get in the ring I used
to say, "I'm gonna murder that bum."
I didn't really meant it.
It was just a sayin', you know?
Sure.
And then you, actually,
and you go and you do it.
Hey, hey...
...these guys are comin' after you.
You gotta defend yourself,
there's nothin' wrong with that.
I bet I know what would make you feel better.
Yeah, well...
...I gotta get to the meeting with Al.
Well, then...
...you can do something
to make me feel better.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
Get him to make me a dancer
at The Four Deuces.
- A dancer?
- Yeah, you know how good I dance.
I don't want you bein' no dancer.
No?
I thought you liked the way I dance.
Yeah, I like the way you dance.
I don't want you dancin'
for no other guys, though.
No?
Okay, I need to get to the meeting.
I think you're gonna be late.
Are you gonna make me a dancer?
I swear to God, that son of a bitch,
he cost me 10 dollars, Al!
- I could have cut his freakin' throat!
- Why didn't you?
The guy was fuckin' my sister,
what am I gonna do, huh?
It'd break her heart, I mean.
I fucked her a time or two myself.
Hey, watch it! What the fuck?
- That's my sister you're talking about!
- Yeah, she's a nice piece of ass.
- You better watch your freakin' mouth.
- Jack, nice of you to stop by.
My apologies, Al.
- I was...
- Gettin' a blowjob from your lady?
It's the only excuse I accept.
So after our little outing last night...
...the cops raided our casinos.
I guess we hit a nerve.
Everybody down!
Fuck!
I'm out.
- Did you throw in?
- I threw in...
- ...you're the one that didn't throw in.
- I threw in!
Bones, stop food dropping me. I know
your little routine that you're pulling.
- That's bullshit, bullshit.
- Alright, keep your eyes on your cards.
I got my cards.
What do you got?
Lookin' good, ladies.
Take a walk. I want to talk to Jack.
Listen, I never had a chance
to thank you for the restaurant.
There's no need.
Yeah, yeah, there is.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't be here right now.
So, I wanted to repay the favor.
What's this?
I'm a man of my word.
Sorry it took me so long.
Baldelli, Tropea, Bascone.
It's the three men
that killed your father, Jackie.
Tropea.
Bascone!
Let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
You're kiddin'?
No, nickel and dime in each of their hands.
Death by machine gun fire.
So, same M.O., and they
all work for the Gennas?
Yep.
Our lucky day.
I told my client he was under
no obligation to appear before you.
But I heard you had some questions for me,
so I thought it was my civic duty to pop in.
Oh, wasn't that nice of you.
Let me ask you something.
Orazio Tropea...
...Vito Bascone.
Is that right?
Ecola Baldelli.
You know those paisans, by any chance?
Yeah, because they were all
machine gunned down here last week.
- That's tragic.
- So, you're denying any responsibility?
Absolutely.
I didn't shoot those men.
Bugs Moran's right hand man Hymie Weiss...
...he was machine gunned down, too...
...right outside the Holy Name
cathedral, no less.
That's terrible.
But I run a used furniture business.
I don't know about such things.
Okay.
I do from time to time
provide liquid refreshments...
...but you guys should know this.
I see a lot of you in my clubs.
Providing alcoholic beverages is
against the law of the land, Mr. Capone.
Then tell people to stop drinking.
The United States congress
put that law on the books...
...to promote the health
and welfare of the American people.
Come on, you expect people to believe that?
That, what, congress jumped because a bunch
of tee-totaling church ladies told them to?
It was Rockefeller and his oil boys!
Cars were made to run on gas or alcohol.
Rockefeller wanted to corner the market.
So, he bribed congress
to put a halt in production...
...of alcohol and now he's making billions.
And you're callin' me the criminal?
Look here, you smelly, greasy wop.
I don't care how you justify what you do.
I don't care the scum in this city
that you got on your payroll.
This is my city you're in and there are
dead bodies on my streets...
...that's a problem.
And what are you gonna do
about it, tough guy?
Since there are no charges,
I believe our business here is done.
Good work, fellas, keep it up.
If they can't take the truth about
this country then fuck 'em!
Jack.
Guys.
What're you hanging out
with a goon like Capone for, Jack?
You know, it's nothin', some part time work.
Driving trucks, whatever.
- 'Cause that's not what people are saying.
- Yeah, you know what they say about rumors?
You can't trust 'em.
I wasn't done talking, Jack.
So I want you to listen to me.
Capone is low-life scum. You understand that?
You wanna pal around with the guineas and
the wops, one of two things gonna happen.
You're gonna be in prison, or you're
gonna end up like your old man.
You wanna do that to your ma?
That's not what your pop would have wanted.
Come on, tell us what we need to know.
Let us help you, Jack.
Like I said, guys, it's just rumors.
Mr. Capone, what are you doing
coming out of police headquarters today?
What, me and the boys? We were
just talking about interior design.
Goddamn it!
Try spreading your feet
a little further apart.
Trust me.
- Not bad, huh?
- Not bad at all.
Been meaning to speak to you
about something, Jack.
We can't just rely on speakeasies
and whorehouses anymore.
I wanna expand into the unions,
pick up the pension funds.
Also, I want you to stop
by the hotels and smoke shops.
Convince them to install slot machines.
- Like in Atlantic City?
- Exactly.
This way instead of waiting on them to
come to us, we bring the action to them.
You know, Al...
...there's something that
I've been meaning to ask you about.
- What's that, Jackie?
- No offense, but...
...how'd you get the scars on your face?
Years ago when I was a bouncer in Brooklyn.
I saw this broad over by the tables.
So I walked up to her, polite-like...
...and I said to her, "You got a nice ass."
Out of nowhere this guy jumped up
from the bar and took out a knife.
He cut the hell out of me.
- Boyfriend?
- No, brother.
The doctors did what they could.
But you know what?
I think it gives me character.
Yeah, sure.
So what'd you do,
did you go back and whack the guy?
No, I hired him.
You can always use a good knife guy, right?
What? The dumb mick moved.
You didn't have your feet
spread far enough apart.
You wanna go again?
No, I don't need no ball.
You know...
...last couple of years...
...our organization here has been suffering.
And I don't just mean financially.
Yeah, no kiddin'.
I can't tell you...
...how many men, good men...
...that behemoth has had killed.
My own brothers,
killed in the street like fuckin' dogs!
And Frankie Yale, Capone had him
shot down in new York just last week.
Yeah, you know why? Because of me...
...because Frankie backed me
to run the Sicilian Union...
...so we don't have to use Capone's man...
...Tony Lombardo, that fat prick.
I think we're all in agreement, here.
We've had a longstanding problem
and it needs to be fixed.
Frank, Pete...
...I'm offering you
50,000 dollars to kill Capone.
But first...
...I want you to take out
his machine gunner, Jack McGurn.
We'll do him for free.
Lulu!
Lulu, I love you!
You're the bee's knees,
you've always been my bee's knees!
Lulu, Lulu.
Come here, Lulu. Lulu, I love you,
I love you, come here. Lulu.
Just... Lulu, Lulu, I love you.
Psst, Lulu!
Marry me, Lulu. Lulu, Lulu, Lulu, look, look.
You can't just come in here and take out
every guy that looks at me twice.
Now you see here...
...I agreed to let you dance,
but I never agreed to that.
Now you listen to me, slugger.
I don't need your permission for anything.
Hell, I don't need any man's permission.
I've gotten myself this far.
Baby.
Baby, I'm sorry.
Look, I got carried away.
Okay, I wasn't thinking.
I just came here to pick you up
and take you home, that's all.
Why don't we get out of here?
I've got a better idea.
Why don't you get out of here.
- Yeah.
- This is Jack...
...all in all we got six
different businesses ready to go.
- That's my boy, Jackie.
- Listen, Al.
If the machines are ready,
I can deliver them tomorrow.
No, no, Anselmi and Scalise
is picking 'em up.
I just want you to focus
on getting more locations.
All right, I'm on it. Just be sure to...
Jackie?
Jackie!
He's lost too much blood.
We're losing him. Hang in there, Jack!
Daddy!
You made it.
I was so scared.
I never lost faith, Jack.
I knew you was a fighter.
I guess it's that boxing mentality, huh?
And don't worry about the bill,
I got that covered.
You just get rested.
When you're better you come see me.
We'll take care of business.
Jack...
...what were you thinking going out
and getting yourself shot up like that?
And don't think you're off the hook
for the other night either, mister.
I'm worried about you.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be okay.
Okay.
Just promise me when you're all
healed up we'll go away somewhere.
Anything you want, sweetheart.
I just...
...I just need some rest.
Goddamn it, he's alive!
McGurn just walked out of the hospital.
What the fuck did I tell you?
- What were you supposed to do?
- Impossible.
- We filled the guy full of holes.
- No, you didn't!
That's how you shoot something full of holes!
I heard Capone is in Palm Beach.
Yeah?
Well, you better hope to God
that he stays there.
Clean this shit up!
- Are the caterers set for next week?
- Yeah, florists too.
- Should be quite the shindig.
- Good, it better be.
Hostin' the D.A.'s no different
in Florida than it is in Chicago.
You want to do business,
you gotta do a little wining and dining.
Look who finally decided to show up.
Oh, my God, it's like a movie set!
Even better, sweetheart...
...it's not make believe.
How you doin', Jackie?
Still a little sore, I'll be alright though.
Louise, how about you go join Rio
in the back? He'll make you a mimosa.
- A what?
- A mimosa.
Champagne with fresh
Florida orange juice in it.
My God, I think I can get used to this.
I appreciate you taking care of things.
Don't mention it. I gotta talk to you
about something, come on.
Sit down, Jack.
I want them, Al.
Easy, Jack.
You gotta play this smart.
You can't just go into
the flower shop and start blastin'.
I know.
I just want to get your blessing
before I go back.
- What's your play?
- Abe Bernstein.
He still runnin' truckloads of whiskey?
That old bastard?
Been sellin' hootch to me, Moran...
...everyone and his fuckin' mother.
And he still owes you for operating
without interference, right?
Go on.
Here's how we do this.
- Yeah.
- Boychick, how are you?
Abe Berstein, you old kike.
Are you still alive?
I'll dance on your grave,
you Irish potato eater.
- What's on your mind, Abe?
- Well, you may have heard, but...
...our old friend 'Mr. Brown'
is down in Miami.
But with him gone,
some of his boys got a little careless.
And one of my guys pinched one of his trucks.
The good stuff, Canadian whiskey.
I can let you have it for fifty bucks a case.
Yeah, well, like I always say...
...any liquor of that fat beast
is liquor of mine.
- When can you deliver it?
- How's tomorrow morning?
- Perfect. You know where my warehouse is?
- 2120 North Clark.
Have them drop it off
at 10 a.m. I'll be there.
Mazel and Brocha.
How's that?
Couldn't have been better.
Give my regards to Al.
Right on time.
- This is for Abe.
- Thanks.
I'm gonna go grab a bite to eat.
I'll be back when you're done unloading.
- You wanna give me a hand with these?
- Fuck that, Frankie. We're on time.
The other guys are late, let them unload it.
What the hell is this?
You got me, boss. Maybe an accident?
Well, cut down one of the side streets.
We're late for the shipment as it is.
Go on, go around them, come on.
Isn't that Moran?
Can't see his face real good.
I mean, yeah, it's gotta be.
Yeah?
We're on our way.
Let's go.
So what have we got?
You got fifty cases,
about a dozen bottles per case.
Once you water it down,
you guys are about fifty grand.
Considerin' we paid Abe
a fourth of that, not too bad.
Who said the Jews were good with money?
Brought her home, you know, slapped her
around a little bit, she likes that.
Alright, everybody,
grab a piece of that wall!
What?
- You heard him, move!
- You boys new to the force?
- You don't know how this works?
- We know how this works, hit the wall.
If you're lookin' for a payoff, we already
paid up this month. But I'll tell you what...
- ...we'll let each of you grab a bottle.
- Shut your mouth and face the wall.
If this is a beef about concealed weapons...
...our lawyers will get that beat
with one phone call.
You think we should give you a phone call?
That's funny, you never let me finish mine.
Where's Moran?
Where the fuck is Moran?
They said he was here!
Wait, wait, wait. Coppers.
- What the hell do they want?
- A bust?
Nah, probably just looking for a payoff.
McGurn, what the hell is he doing here?
Boss, we gotta go.
Boss, we gotta go!
You want us to go after McGurn?
No, just drive.
You know, up till now the people of Chicago
have looked on these gangland killings...
...almost like entertainment.
A little radio drama in the morning
they can listen to over their corn flakes.
But this is sick.
I think this might actually
be a good thing for us.
Good, how?
One of the dead men was just
a mechanic, another was an optician...
...who just liked to pal around
with tough guys.
If men like these can be
lined up and gunned down...
...then your average person
is going to feel no one is safe.
The public's finally going to demand
that these men be taken down.
But how does that help us do our job?
We can never get witnesses to come forward.
We can't make arrests stick.
Which is why Mr. Hoover has decided
to go after Capone on tax fraud.
Doesn't matter what the charges are
when half the damn cops in the city...
...are on Capone's payroll.
Our bureau is going to drag Mr. Capone
into court on federal charges, Detective.
In the meantime, I suggest you and your
men round up the rest of these criminals...
...on whatever charges you can think up.
Now...
...if you gentlemen don't mind,
we'd like some privacy.
Do you believe the way that O'Connor
was kissing that G-man's ass?
I mean, it was like...
You know what? You can play
the fool with everybody else...
...but your bullshit doesn't fly with me.
- Where's McGurn?
- Get your fuckin'...
Maybe you have not noticed,
I'm not part of your little boys club.
I don't play by those rules
or those fake codes.
I'm gonna ask you one more time,
Detective, once.
Where's McGurn?
Chicago's so cold in the winter.
When are we gonna go to Florida again?
I already told ya. I'll give Al a call,
we'll see what happens.
- Who's that?
- I ordered room service.
Again?
What d'ya got, a hollow leg?
I'm taking you in, kid.
- What for?
- You're under arrest...
...for suspicion of murder
in the Valentine's Day massacre.
- He was here with me the whole time!
- You tell that to the judge, sweetheart.
- We're going to bring you in as well.
- What's the charge?
Taking a woman across state lines for
immoral purposes. That good enough?
You both conspired to violate the Mann act.
You fucked up, Jack.
You fucked up.
Take a seat, Jack.
Did you rat me out, Jack?
What kind of question is that?
It's a pretty fucking good question.
After everything I've done for you.
You're gonna ask me that question?
Who brought you up, Jack?
You may have started me...
...but I earned my way up.
Yeah, but I can fuckin' take it
away from you, can't I?
The word is that the cops and the feds...
...they're pretty embarrassed
by your court appearance today.
And they're gonna keep coming
after you any way they can.
So until things blow over,
I need to ask you a favor.
Yeah, what's that?
I need you to lay low.
I need you to move out to the suburbs.
Be in charge of collecting.
Al, come on.
You want me to be a bag man in the 'burbs?
It's just for a little while.
It's a death sentence.
Al, we need you out here, it's important.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Listen, Jack, thanks for understanding.
You'll be back here in no time.
Alphonse Capone...
...you have been found guilty
of violation of federal tax law...
...for the years 1925 through 1929.
You will be confined
to a federal penitentiary...
- What?
- ...for not less than 10 years.
You can't do this!
Who the fuck do you think you are?
- Escort Mr. Capone out of the court room.
- Do you know who I am?
Do you fuckin' know who I am!
I'm fuckin' Al Capone!
You fuckin' better remember me!
You didn't like
your Valentine's dinner I made?
Yeah, baby, it was great.
I was just thinking back when I was a kid.
I was thinking about who I used to be.
Just a kid who wanted to box.
Make some prize money,
take care of my family.
I just can't help but wonder...
...if the Gennas had just left my pop alone.
I don't know who I'm supposed to be anymore.
Al's gone. Frank Nitti's
runnin' the south side...
...he don't want nothin' to do
with the old gang.
- I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
- I'll tell you what you're supposed to do.
You're supposed to sit there,
looking at me and be happy.
Did you forget, mister?
Walking into that dressing room
seven years ago and giving me this?
How could I forget?
It's the smartest thing I ever did.
Well.
I actually think of today
as our anniversary...
...and not the day we actually got married.
And I think we should celebrate.
You're right.
I'll go get us some champagne.
Good.
Take a little walk,
see if I can get out of this funk.
You...
...I love you so much.
I love you.
Practicing for the tournament?
A hundred bucks is a hundred bucks.
Yeah, you can buy your girl
a lot of candy and flowers with that.
I actually gotta go pick up some champagne.
Celebrating, huh?
Hey, you remember February 14th
from a few years ago, right?
Nah, I can barely remember
what I was doing yesterday.
Maybe this'll help remind you.
Happy Valentine's Day, Jack.